Leave no soul unturned.
Wishmaster 4: The Prophecy Fulfilled is a horror,
fantasy film directed by Chris Angel.
The unspeakable evil of the soul-devouring djinn rises again in this fourth
electrifying installment of the unstoppable Wishmaster horror legacy!
But now, as a host of new victims see their most nightmarish wishes come true, the world faces the ultimate
demonic terror: an onslaught of multiple djinns hell-bent on destroying everything in their path!
Lisa, played by Tara Spencer-Nairn.
Verdel, played by Michael Trucco.
Sam, played by Jason Thompson.
Djinn, played by John Novak.
Hunter, played by Victor Webster.
Hollister, played by John Benjamin Martin.
Wishmaster: The Prophecy Fulfilled is a 2002 Canadian dark fantasy horror film directed by Chris Angel and starring
Michael Trucco, Tara Spencer-Nairn, Jason Thompson, Victor Webster, Kimberly Huie, and John Novak.
It is the fourth and final installment of the Wishmaster film series.
The film explores themes of wheelchair, hell, sequel, death.
The tone is dark.